takingyouforward.com 2016-11-02

# Privacy Policy - Taking You Forward Inc.

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Taking You Forward, Inc. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.takingyouforward.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Taking You Forward, Inc.

Personal identification information  
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, subscribe to our newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information  
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Web browser cookies  
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

How we use collected information  
Taking You Forward, Inc. collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * To improve customer service – We may use information you provide to help us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * To personalize user experience – We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * To improve our Site – We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * To process transactions – We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * To send periodic emails – The email address Users provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  * To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature – To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.

How we protect your information  
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices, and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. 

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over an SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

Sharing your personal information  
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Electronic newsletters  
If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

Changes to this privacy policy  
Taking You Forward, Inc. has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms  
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

SLL Bldg., P. Remedio Street, Mandaue City, 6014 Cebu, Philippines

Australia (AU)  
Local: [(02) 8317 4305](tel:283174305)  
Intl: [+61 (2) 8317 4305](tel:61283174305)

United Kingdom (UK)  
Local: [(20) 3318 5344](tel:2033185344)  
Intl: [+44 (20) 3318 5344](tel:442033185344)

America (US)  
Local: [(312) 757 2814](tel:3127572814)  
Intl: [+1 (312) 757 2814](tel:13127572814)

Canada (CA)  
Local: [(514) 500 4394](tel:5145004394)  
Intl: [+1 (514) 500 4394](tel:15145004394)

Email:[  
info@takingyouforward.com](mailto:info@takingyouforward.com)  
Website:[  
www.takingyouforward.com](http://www.takingyouforward.com/)
